Thank you for watching
me
none
We're having a Halloween game tournament with teams dressed up in costumes requested by each other.
The Maguto team will be punished with a horrible game, and this time both teams are serious about the game, so who will win?
Let's play the next game!
Balance
The two teams will be holding a treasure chest between their legs like a bajon, and supporting the other machine with one finger in a balance duel.
The team that remains until the end gets points.
Are you sure you can do it?
I understand, but I wonder if I can do it.
You can do it anywhere by yourself.
I can do this forever.
I can probably do it with any finger.
Any finger you like.
Let's go... get ready for the Demon King's big balance.
Let go of my fingers.
That's great.
Either one or both of them are crooked.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there!
Cat duel!
Oh, it's moving!
Oh, it's going to collide with you!
Ganbatte ganbatte
ah... persimmon is moving... persimmon...
Got it!
Shiroko won!
Wow, wow, wow!
It's a catfight right from the start.
Tamura the white cat wins with great consistency. White Cat Tamura Wins with Outstanding Stability
In the second round, the four of us faced off against each other.
Costumes are so important!
The delicatessen shop is strong!
Let's go!
Prepare the magic treasure balance!
Here we go.
Let go of my hand!
The delicatessen!
The delicatessen.
No movement
End.
All right, over and out.
Red Hood wins.
Now...
Kawasaki says the Red Hood is the last one to get hit with the treasure chest.
Endo, you're dressed like this, so I thought you wouldn't last long.
But it's no good.
It was a no-go!
Strength.
It's like an extension of my part-time job.
So...
The balance of a treasure trove of ultra-short term work.
In the end, in this world
Yumiki can do anything.
I can't do this.
You're a bus driver.
Extended work hours...
You're playing hard to get.They're playing so much.
Have you ever done this kind of thing before?
I used to do it a lot.
I did.
They called me a pro because I could do it with my pinky.
My school
I can do it with my pinky.
I can do this forever.
Here we go. Get ready.
Here we go.
Let's do it.
You did it, you did it, you did it.
Finish.
Victory!
I'm so tired, aren't I?
I was already doing so much
I was doing it!
This game is really interesting.
I could play a hundred rounds and still not fill the scale.
It's true.
Next, we had the "Aloin Basket" game, which we played last time.
The members who corresponded to the theme that was given at Fuji
The members who couldn't sit at the table
The member who couldn't sit down becomes the next demon.
The team that could get all the members to sit down gets one point.
Tonight, we had eight members.
The first two are Yumiki, and the fourth is decided.
Yumiki, you have to move a little harder.
That's right.
But that means you. But that's just me.
I'll do my best to be one and the same.
Come on, Yota, let's go.
Let's go.
Those of you who made even the slightest mistake in the choreography on the national tour...
All right, let's go!
All of you, all of you.
All of you!
Aaaaahhh!
I moved my boo-boo.
I made a mistake with the snow.
I was so excited about the opening that I made a slight mistake with one of them.
I'm in the middle of a different area area.
I'm in the middle of a different area.
I'm sure you've made mistakes too.
I see...
I'm an actuary... an actuary...
I'm an actuary... I'm an actuary... when I was going to be filmed, I thought too much that I was going to be filmed... and I made all the mistakes because everyone would know that I was going to be filmed.
I had to do it all in a cool way.
But the viewers don't really understand what we're trying to do, even if we think we're doing it right, but we're not.
I've been doing it for a long time, but lately I feel like I'm suddenly going blank.
I was taken out of the picture, and somehow I moved in Nero's head, so I didn't have to move where I didn't have to move.
I went back with a big smile on my face, so I guess it's better to go back with a big smile on my face, and I can go back with a big smile on my face, too.
But then again, the fact that Yumeki's standing there earns him some funny points.
Hmm...
People who wash their bath towels every day.
Okay, let's start!
I'm done!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Watch out, watch out, watch outDangerous.
Good one.
Well, you could wash it every day.
On the other hand, how many of you haven't moved?
Oh, two days.
Two days.
No, that's right.
Do you think you don't have to do it that many times?
I'll give you two days.
Yes, two days.
Yes, the other
Yakeda...
Yes, YUKEDA
I don't use bath towels.
I got it, what, what do you mean?
I use a lot of smaller towels.
why?
What is that?
I have to use a very large hanger when I do laundry.
Towels that can be used with small hangers.
So you use face towels?
Yes, for hair and body.
I might have made a mistake.
People who wash their towels every day are moving.
I thought you use a clean towel every day.
No, that's what I meant.
Oh, that's what I mean.
I don't wash them every day.
I mean you don't wash them yourself. I mean, you're not washing yourself.
I'm washing it.
Oh, that's okay.
I've got a few in stock that you can use.
I didn't wash them.
But you use a new one every day, don't you?
Of course.
Then you can move on.
Oh, good.
But I can't. I'm standing.
Oh, no.
I didn't sit down.
Pumpkin team point awarded.
Yay!
Okay, here we go. Subject.
Are you sure you don't mind if I take just one picture?
And the one that keeps huffing and puffing is Yumiki.
I keep hearing the sound of the dinosaurs.
Okay, let's go. Here's your subject.
Have you ever had a psychic experience?
Let's start!
Ghost experience
Okay, that's it.
This move was a bust.
Three people moved.
I thought everyone had one.
Hey...
I mean, doesn't everyone in Nogizaka have one?
That's right.
I was in Nogizaka a long time ago, at a famous hotel. I was at that famous hotel that was in Nogi a long time ago.
Oh, I see.
The one where the elevator takes you to Uchiumi.
I've been in that elevator too.
I see, scary!
I've never seen that before.
I've felt it
No way, what did you see?
What did you see?
I don't think it's strange when I see something that doesn't seem strange to me.
It's just too human.
How do you know?
In retrospect, you don't really look at passers-by that seriously, do you?
But when I think back on it, I wonder why that person was barefoot.
What?
He was barefoot and no one was wondering why.
It's like it's invisible.
I see.
Scary.
I thought about it later.
And Ikeda moved.
He moved.
I was in a hotel in the middle of a heavenly tour.
This time.
Yes, sir.
It seems to happen every year, and I was talking with the members about how it's going to happen again this year.
Yes.Oh, my God.
What kind of experience is that?
I've been getting shaken up in the middle of the night, and it's been going on and on and on and on and on and on and on.
And then the water rushing out of the tap.
What?
In the room.
The waterworks in your room.
That's right.
Which tap?
I don't know.
Then which one?
But when I told that to the people around me...
I'm like, "Oh, yeah.
Huh?
I don't know.
Mr. Michisaki is nodding his head.
We were in the next room the same day.
I had a curtain on my bathtub.
I didn't have a window or anything, but it was moving the whole time I was in there.
And even after I closed the door, it kept moving in the bathtub.
I don't know...
But still, there's a fan on top, so it must be moving.
Is that so?
Which one?
But I don't think it's scary.
Did someone come in here?
But it was like 3:00 a.m., right?
Well, people come even at 3 a.m.
That's scary. I'm scared.
I'm sure you've seen the jar because the hotel is connected to the beach, and you can hear the water and stuff.
Did you see the jar?
No, I'm too scared to look there.
I'm too scared to look.
Maybe you're wrong.
Maybe you're not.
No, it's very scary.
I've been scared a few times, but the last one I made a video of.
Aaaaah!
What do you mean?
When I went away for the shooting of a music video, I stayed overnight at a hotel.
The room was on the third or fourth floor, and even though the door was closed, I heard a thumping sound from outside.
I was already on the fourth floor or something, so there was no way it was coming from outside.
And the curtains are closed, but it's shaking as if it's sticking to my fingers.
Only a part of it?
Yes, it was there.
Yes, I had it.
I had it too.
Scary, scary!
Dorr.
Wow!
The windows... the windows...
Yeah, the curtains were shaking and thumping.
I was so scared that I opened the window and saw a torii gate.
And there was a torii gate!
There was no torii gate outside the window.
I told you it was there.
You said it was because of something else.
I'm scared.That's kind of scary.
No, it's not.
No, I'm just...
I'm in the 50s, and my shoulder hurts.
Just when I say "wah", it goes "ding".
It's like a "ding!
I shouldn't have done that.
I was wrong.
Well, points to the pumpkin team, then.
Next is the last one.
Hiramoto, what's your question?
I hope everyone moves.
Who hasn't eaten breakfast today?
Ready, go!
Those who haven't eaten
Wait a minute.
What the hell is this?
Wait a minute... wait a minute... this is a deliberation.
If you haven't eaten, you have to move.
I'm sorry.
You haven't eaten?
No, I haven't.
You haven't eaten.
Here we go.
Yay!
That's a nice win.
What's with this last part?
You're eating a lot, aren't you?
We usually do.
Only today... we had motsu nabe and gyoza last night. I ate last night's motsu-nabe and gyoza only today.
I didn't eat because I had a stomach upset.
I usually eat rice with egg.
I didn't eat it.
Only today I couldn't eat.
Oh, everyone else ate?
You're all so neat, aren't you?
What are you eating?
Scrambled eggs, broccoli and meat.
Where's the cake?
Two cheinmuscat.
So-so, so-so.
I didn't expect that.
I had natto rice.
You're good.
What about you, Inoue?
Are you eating?
I did.
What did you eat?
I had basashi today.
Is it out?
Yes, I did.
I can't believe you're wearing a lion's head.
You had baby bass?
We get a lot of frozen ones this size.
Put them in the fridge the night before.
One package is not so big that it fills you up.
It's just right.
Isn't it amazing? Two people eating basashi in the morning.
What kind of basashi don't you want to eat at night? I don't want to eat at night, Basashi.
It's true, it's true, it's true.
Why do you want to eat it the next morning?
What?
I only heard the fan.
I didn't mean to bother you so much.
It's just... maybe we should eat the protein in the morning.
That's what I was thinking.
Yumiki...
Fried rice and green peppers.
What is she doing?
Fried rice is also kind of awesome!
What's a green bell pepper?
It's some kind of sweet and spicy fried green pepper.
She eats it in the morning.
I made it myself.
Fried rice?
Fried rice in the morning?
Sounds like something I'd eat.
I drained the yogurt and ate it.
It makes the yogurt hard.
Why not if it's soft?
It's watery.
Wow...
It really does look like a witch.
Sounds like a scary story.
Let's play the next game. Himeimura, please.
Let's go!
Pumpkin fan relay! Pumpkin fan relay!
Yay!
Relay showdown using handheld fans to carry balloons that look like pumpkins.
Each team of 4 participants
relay the balloons and fans to the next person and back twice around the course
The last person has to compete with the fastest time to put the fan in the box at the goal.
First, the team members will face off. Yumiki and Ioki will be in charge of the anchor.
If you fall off, you can use your hand.
And you're not allowed to roll it while it's still taut.
We've got uniforms.
Second, fourth, and last, Yumiki. Dinosaur!
No, I'm really here to win today. I've put it in that box.
Until the last one gets in there.
Let's get ready to go.
Good, good, good, good.
It's time to settle in.
Come on, come on, come on. Mr. Himura is close.
I'm in the way. Mr. Himura is in the way.
Second, second, second, second.
Make sure you carry him with you.
Are you a fan?
Don't push me with a fan.
Keep going to the side.
Don't push it with the fan.
Don't cross the line and give it to me
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Please pass it across the line
Go, go, go, go.
Come on, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third, third.
Good match, good match Good game, good game, good game
It's a good match.
When the white cat moves, you hear a bell.
Reversal or reversal?
Yes, yes, yes.
Almost at the same time Almost at the same time
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That guy...
Oh, no!
Yumeki yumeki baka baka baka baka baka baka baka baka
When I play it, it's down, it's down, get out, get out...
Come on, please.
I can do it! I can do it!
We're getting close...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
You win if you let me in, you win if you let me in.
I'm in!
The green pumpkin is in!
The ghost team wins!
Last but not least, we almost gave it to them at the same time.
Yumeki got a little flustered, but at the end, it was a game of "get it in".
You're a little rusty, aren't you?
I'm so disappointed.I'm sorry to hear that.
It's so frustrating.
Before we started, Ume and I were saying we're going to win for sure.
The moment Ume and Endo lost over here, you looked super disappointed.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's really great what you did with the dinosaurs.
That's amazing.
I think there might have been a little bit of a costume call.
That's what's so disappointing.
I'd love to do that.
Let's see if the pumpkin team can make up for it in the second round.
If the pumpkin team doesn't win, they'll be in trouble if they get 4 points.
Here we go, here we go!
Go, go, go, go!
Mr. Imura's interrupting and doing it again.
Don't get out of the heavens!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Kamakiri, here he comes!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
If it falls, you can do it with your hands
Should I take it slow?
Go, go, go, go, go!
Kamakiri, if it falls, lift it up with your hand.
go, go, go, go
Oh, no, no, no!
Kamakiri, what are you doing?
Here comes the big brake for Kuromi Kamakiri!
In the blink of an eye, he gives up a one-man lead!
Oh!Ooh!
Here comes the anchor... the pumpkin team anchor.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no.
I'm down!
It's getting sad, sad, sad.
We've got to hit it from below!
I still don't get it.
But even the anchor, Kawasaki, couldn't get into the box at all.
In the meantime, Kuromi managed to make it to Sakaguchi.
Anchor got one minute to win!
If you put it in, you win!
Will there be a great comeback?
Will orange be in?
Don't worry!
This is gonna be tough.
Green's going in.
I can do it. I can do it.
Yes!
It's a complete turnaround!
This is... this is... this was a big brake for Kuromi.
Thank you very much.
I'm really happy for you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
And now, I'd like to announce the members for the 34th single, all bag sizes.
Each time a new single is released, a member is selected to perform that song.
Nogizaka46 Nogizaka46
Here is the formation this time
Double center formation with two members in the center.
The first one is Mao Ioki from the 3rd row.
Next, the name was called out...
Nao Tomisato
Nao Tomisato, a 5th term student, was selected for the first time
When I was born, when I arrived at my position
I thought about my fans who always support me
I wondered if they would be happy to see me in the selection.
I want to make myself known to everyone more and more.
I want to make myself known to everyone more and more, and I want to appeal myself to the public.
Next, Haruka Kuromi was called by name.
Haruka Kuromi, a 4th term student, was selected for the first time.
I'm feeling a bit anxious at the moment.
But I'm really thankful to all the fans and staffs who support me on a daily basis.
There may not be so much I can do now, but
I would like to do my best to repay the favor even if it's just one thing.
Thank you very much.
Next, Kazuki Mukai was called by name.
Kazuki Mukai, a 3rd term student, was selected for the first time.
I'm really looking forward to it. The third term members all congratulated me.
I've been surrounded by my peers like that.
I want to make this single to cherish the time with my classmates and members.
Third row, followed by Yumikinao and Yuna Shibata.
Miku Ichinose
Satsuki Sugawara
The last one in the third row is Yu Atsushi, followed by Mayu Tamura in the second row.
Mayu Tamura
Minami UmezawaMinami Umezawa
Teresa Ikeda
Sakura Kawasaki
Renca Iwamoto
Yuki Yoda
Nagi Inoue
First row at the end Shiori Kubo
Mizuki Yamashita
And the center of the 34th single is Sakura Endo
Kakihara
Endo and Kaki, both from the 4th term, will double as the center.
I'm not sure if it's possible or not.
I feel that I'm not in a position to say such things, so I'm wondering if this will be a period where I have to think more about the group.
I think this is a period when I have to think more about the group.
I have many ideals, but I don't realize that I can't be as good as the predecessors who have held the center position in the past.
I have many ideals, but since I realized that I can never be as good as the predecessors who have stood at the center of the group in the past.
I have to do my best to do what I can do.
Is this the second time for you to greet the end of the year with those who are going back to their home countries?
I want to be able to work with them with peace of mind.
I want to be able to work with them in a safe environment, and I hope that it will be a period when the seniors can leave everything to us without worrying about us.
I hope that the new Nogizaka will show us what kind of brilliance they have in store for us as we close out this year.
50 times 50 times 50 times is pretty good.
That's pretty good.
Congratulations!
I think it's the best ever.
Aww...
Awww!
Tickets for the live streaming of "Shinyama Mono Live" are now on sale!
I'm Mukai Mukai, a 3rd term student.
This week I went out to dinner with Den-chan.This week I went out to dinner with Den-chan.
Next week, I'm going to have dinner with Ayame!
Yay!
Please subscribe to our channel!